let questions = [{
    question: "How many feet above sea-level is the summit of Mount Everest?",
    choices: ["27,940", "25,771", "29,029", "38,400"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "Which two countries do the summit-point of Mount Everest divide?",
    choices: ["Nepal and India", "Nepal and Myanmar", "China and Pakistan", "Nepal and China"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "What year was the first official ascent of Mount Everest?",
    choices: ["1953", "1952", "1924", "1891"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: "What is the name of the guides who help climbers reach the summit?",
    choices: ["mountain people", "shepards", "climber helpers", "sherpas"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "What is the deadliest part of the climb of Mount Everest?",
    choices: ["Khumbu icefall", "the summit", "the death zone", "south col"],
    correctAnswer: 0
},{
    question: "Generally, how long does the expedition last for one to climb Mount Everest?",
    choices: ["about a day and a half", "2-3 days", "2 months", "6 weeks"],
    correctAnswer: 2
},{
    question: "What's the standard route for climbing Mount Everest?",
    choices: ["southeast Nepal route", "north Chinese route", "east route", "the Alaskan igloo route"],
    correctAnswer: 0
},{
    question: "What is the famous step a climber must negotiate?",
    choices: ["Norgay step", "Khumbu step", "Tibetan step", "Hillary step"],
    correctAnswer: 3
},{
    question: "Which is not something that has been done on Mount Everest?",
    choices: ["skiing down part of the mountain", "helicopter landing on summit", "snow-mobile driven to the summit", "hot air balloon flown over summit"],
    correctAnswer: 2
},{
    question: "What month of the year do most climbers attempt to summit Everest?",
    choices: ["July", "December", "August", "May"],
    correctAnswer: 3
},];
